validnumber.com 2019-12-04

# Privacy Policy | Valid Number

The privacy policy notice on this page discloses the ways how Valid Number (validnumber.com) handles the personal information of its users. This privacy policy applies solely to the use of this website. If a user visits any external website linked from here, they will be subjected to the privacy policy of that particular external website.

**Information Collection**  
Valid Number tracks your system-related information when you visit the website. Such system?related information is collected mainly in the form of server logs by our servers that run various services required to keep this website functional. Besides, when you report any phone number or register for an account, we collect some information that may allow us to trace back to you, if needed. 

**Purpose for Information Collection**  
The information we collect may be used to personalize your experience. For example, system may suggest you the phone number based on the location determined through your IP address. Your information also helps us improve the website based on your feedbacks. In addition, the information you submit when you report a phone number is shown to other users of the website, so they can benefit from the information you share with the community. 

**Information Protection**  
At Valid Number, user's privacy is our highest priority. We never share or sell your personal information, unless required by the law in certain circumstances. 

To protect your session-related information when you visit our website, your information is transmitted through a SSL (Secure Socket Layer), which is a standard technology to encrypt and transmit data over the Internet. 

**Cookie Usage**  
Valid Number uses cookies to keep records of some information on your computer that helps us offer you a personalized experience on this website. You can disable cookies on your Web Browser, if you do not want this website to create any cookie on your machine. If you do disable cookies, some features on the website may not be available to you. 

**Information Disclosure**  
Valid Number, under no circumstances, shares any personally identifiable information of its users with any third-party, unless required by law. In some situations, information that cannot attributed to any particular user may be shared to third-party for research, marketing, or other purposes. 

**COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act)**  
To use Valid Number, you have to be at least 13 years of age. Please DO NOT use this website if you are not at least 13 years old. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We take great precautions to protect your privacy, which help us stay in compliant with California Online Privacy Protection Act. Your information is not distributed to any third party, without your consent. If you create an account on this website, you can, at anytime, login and update your profile to change your information. 

**Policy Changes**  
We may change these privacy policies at any time. If any such change occurs, we will notify you either on this website or through your e-mail (if you have registered for an account). Whenever you use this website, please be sure to visit this page to check our latest privacy policy. 

**Contact**  
If you have any question regarding this policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://validnumber.com/doc/contact "Contact Us").
